<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Dexiong Chen</title>
    <link>https://claying.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Dexiong Chen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://claying.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://claying.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://claying.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description> An Optimal Transport Kernel for Feature Aggregation and its Relationship to Attention Grégoire Mialon, Dexiong Chen, Alexandre d&amp;rsquo;Aspremont, Julien Mairal Preprint, 2020   Convolutional Kernel Networks for Graph-Structured Data Dexiong Chen, Laurent Jacob, Julien Mairal In ICML, 2020   Recurrent Kernel Networks Dexiong Chen, Laurent Jacob, Julien Mairal In NeurIPS, 2019 and accepted as an oral presentation in MLCB, 2019    A Kernel Perspective for Regularizing Deep Neural Networks Alberto Bietti, Grégoire Mialon, Dexiong Chen, Julien Mairal In ICML, 2019    Biological Sequence Modeling with Convolutional Kernel Networks Dexiong Chen, Laurent Jacob, Julien Mairal In Research in Computational Molecular Biology (RECOMB), 2019 and Bioinformatics, 2019     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software</title>
      <link>https://claying.github.io/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://claying.github.io/software/</guid>
      <description>OTK Optimal transport kernel (OTK) is a kernel for feature aggregation. It allows to perform adaptive pooling (attention + pooling). Principally, it can be useful to model any data represented as sets of features (sequences, images, graphs etc.). In this implementation, it can be used as a module in neural networks, or alone as a kernel method. GCKN Graph convolutional kernel networks (GCKN) is a software package to model graph-structured data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>https://claying.github.io/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://claying.github.io/talks/</guid>
      <description> Protein Fold Recognition with Recurrent Kernel Networks. MLCB, Vancouver, 2019.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://claying.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://claying.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description> Teaching assistant for graduate courses  2018-2019 Kernel methods for machine learning, MVA master - ENS Paris Saclay. 2018-2019 Advanced learning models, MSIAM master - Grenoble University. 2017-2018 Kernel methods for machine learning, MVA master - ENS Paris Saclay. 2017-2018 Advanced learning models, MSIAM master - Grenoble University.  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>