<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Dexiong Chen</title>
    <link>https://claying.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Dexiong Chen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://claying.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://claying.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://claying.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description> Unsupervised Manifold Alignment with Joint Multidimensional Scaling Dexiong Chen, Bowen Fan, Carlos Oliver, Karsten Borgwardt Preprint, 2022   Approximate Network Motif Mining via Graph Learning Carlos Oliver, Dexiong Chen, Vincent Mallet, Pericles Philippopoulos, Karsten Borgwardt Preprint, 2022   Structure-Aware Transformer for Graph Representation Learning Dexiong Chen, Leslie O&amp;rsquo;Bray, Karsten Borgwardt ICML, 2022    GraphiT: Encoding Graph Structure in Transformers Grégoire Mialon, Dexiong Chen, Margot Selosse, Julien Mairal Preprint, 2021   Structured Data Modeling with Deep Kernel Machines and Applications in Computational Biology Dexiong Chen PhD thesis, Université Grenoble Alpes, 2020  An Optimal Transport Kernel for Feature Aggregation and its Relationship to Attention Grégoire Mialon, Dexiong Chen, Alexandre d&amp;rsquo;Aspremont, Julien Mairal ICLR, 2021    Convolutional Kernel Networks for Graph-Structured Data Dexiong Chen, Laurent Jacob, Julien Mairal In ICML, 2020    Recurrent Kernel Networks Dexiong Chen, Laurent Jacob, Julien Mairal In NeurIPS, 2019 and accepted as an oral presentation in MLCB, 2019    A Kernel Perspective for Regularizing Deep Neural Networks Alberto Bietti, Grégoire Mialon, Dexiong Chen, Julien Mairal In ICML, 2019    Biological Sequence Modeling with Convolutional Kernel Networks Dexiong Chen, Laurent Jacob, Julien Mairal In Research in Computational Molecular Biology (RECOMB), 2019 and Bioinformatics, 2019     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software</title>
      <link>https://claying.github.io/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://claying.github.io/software/</guid>
      <description>GraphiT GraphiT is an instance of transformers designed for graph-structured data. It takes as input a graph seen as a set of its node features, and incorporate the graph structure via i) relative positional encoding using kernels on graphs and ii) encoding local substructures around each node, such as short paths, before adding it to the node features. OTK Optimal transport kernel (OTK) is a kernel for feature aggregation. It allows to perform adaptive pooling (attention + pooling).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>https://claying.github.io/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://claying.github.io/talks/</guid>
      <description> Structured Data Modeling with Deep Kernel Machines and Applications in Computational Biology. PhD defense, Grenoble, 2020. Convolutional Kernel Networks for Graph-Structured Data. ICML, Virtual, 2020. Protein Fold Recognition with Recurrent Kernel Networks. MLCB, Vancouver, 2019.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://claying.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://claying.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Teaching assistant for graduate courses  2018-2019 Kernel methods for machine learning, MVA master - ENS Paris Saclay. 2018-2019 Advanced learning models, MSIAM master - Grenoble University. 2017-2018 Kernel methods for machine learning, MVA master - ENS Paris Saclay. 2017-2018 Advanced learning models, MSIAM master - Grenoble University.  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
